'Cause every time I see your face
I can't help but fall from grace
This girl's good.
Yeah, a song with rhyming words!
I never thought of that before.
I like her.
Why? Because she can both sing
and play guitar at the same time?
That's all I'm looking for
from these people.
Look at you, all jealous.
Come on, Pheebs. You two have
completely different styles.
She's more....
You know?
And you're more....
Say you'll stay beside me
See? Everybody else is
happy she's done.
Okay, my next song's called:
"Phoebe Buffay, What Can I Say?
I Loved When We Were...
...Singing Partners and I Shouldn't
Have Left You That Way."
One of those "look for
the hidden meaning" songs.
The One With Phoebe's Ex-Partner
Hey, Phoebe.
Hey, Leslie.
How'd you know I'd be here?
I saw Vlad at the place
where they sell the big fish.
He said you played here a lot, so....
I have to go to the bathroom.
If "big-fish place"
comes up again...
... I'd like to know if that's several
big fish or just one big fish.
So Phoebe says you write jingles.
Actually, I said she abandoned me
to write jingles.
Anything we might've heard of?
Home is never far away
Home is Homestar Stew.
But I don't do that anymore.
I got kind of sick of it.
And then I couldn't come up with
anything good, so they fired me.
Bummer.
Well, you know, I was just....
I was just thinking
and just hoping that...
... maybe you'd want
to get back together?
No, but, thanks.
Come on, Phoebe.
Would you just think about it?
No, but, thanks.
See you, Pheebs.
That was kind of brutal.
Let this be a lesson to all of you.
Once you betray me,
I become like the lce Woman.
I'm just very cold, hard, unyielding.
You know, nothing can
penetrate this icy exterior.
Can I have a tissue?
Is someone in there?
I'm playing a daredevil game...
...called "Wait Until the Last Moment
Before I Burst and Die."
Jeez, man! Did you fall?
Hi!
So did you?
Did you fall high?
Someone was in the ladies' room.
I couldn't wait.
I left the lid up for you, though.
You know what, Gunther?
Go ahead.
I'm talking to....
This is where you say your name.
Ginger.
I'm talking to Ginger, so...
Don't you have to use the bathroom?
No, I just
I'd rather talk to you.
Yes, I do.
Yes, I do have to go to the bathroom.
There's someone in here.
-Where's Chandler?
-He can't make it.
He said he had to go back
to his job and
Joey?
Joey Tribbiani?
I can see you, okay?
You're hiding behind the coats.
Close one.
Hi.
Hi, sweetie.
Hello.
Hey, Ross.
-I've got some bad news.
-What?
I can eat,
but I have to come back here.
Come on. You've worked late
every night for two weeks.
-What is it now?
-It's my fault. I quit today.
But work comes first!
But that's sad about you, though.
What happened?
What happened? Burn out?
Burn all out, did you?
He's leaving for a better job.
That's great.
So I guess this is goodbye then.
Goodbye.
Okay, then.
Well, we're gonna
miss you around here.
Yeah, me too.
-So see you on Saturday.
-Yeah, you bet!
Now, you know those
are a delicacy in lndia.
That was Leslie calling
to see if we can get back together.
It's like the 20th time today.
Yeah, good luck, Leslie.
She must've hurt you bad.
Well, yeah.
You know, we were best friends...
...ever since we were little.
Our moms worked on the barge together.
You two must've been so cute,
running around on a barge.
You never run on a barge!
Is Chandler around?
He met some girl at the coffeehouse.
Ginger something.
Sure it wasn't something that sounded
liked Ginger? Like "Gingeer"?
No, it was Ginger.
I remember because
when he told me, I said:
The movie star
Oh, man!
That's the girl I was hiding from.
When she sees he's my roommate,
she'll tell him what I did.
What did you do?
Oh, no! I can't....
I can't tell you. It's the
most awful thing I've ever done.
Don't tell us.
We'll wait till Chandler gets home.
It'll be more fun that way.
It was, like, four years ago.
Ginger and I had gone out a few times.
Then one weekend...
...we went to her Dad's cabin...
...just me, her and her
annoying little dog, Pepper.
That night I cooked
this really romantic dinner
You gave her food poisoning!
I wish.
After dinner, me, her and Pepper
fell asleep in front of the fire.
I woke up in the middle of the night
and saw the fire was dying out...
...so I picked up a log
and threw it on.
Or what I thought was a log.
Oh, my God!
You threw Pepper on the fire!
I wish.
Another thing I probably
should've told you about Ginger...
...is that she kind of has a...
...artificial leg.
Oh, my God!
What did you do after
you threw her leg on the fire?
I ran!
That's the best kiss I've had...
...with anybody I met
in a men's room.
Actually, me too.
Foot all in the puddle!
Damn! I hate that!
-You'll have to get out of those shoes.
-Don't worry.
No, really.
You're gonna freeze.
No, I'm not.
You're not?
Have you got a bionic foot?
Someday. Maybe.
Funny book?
I'm just thinking about
something funny I heard today.
Mark saying,
"I'll see you Saturday."
Yeah, at the lecture.
I told you last week.
You said you didn't mind.
It's not the lecture I mind.
Please tell me it's not because
I'm going with Mark.
-Well
-Oh, my God!
I'm sorry, but if you're not
working with him anymore...
...why do you still hang out?
Because he's my friend.
But do you really need
another "friend"?
If I stop playing with Joey
and Chandler, can I play with Mark?
Is that funny?
Am I suppose to be laughing?
I don't know. You thought
"See you Saturday" was funny.
Mark is in fashion.
I like having a friend
I can share this stuff with.
You guys would never
go to a lecture with me.
I'd love to go with you.
Really?
I have clothes.
I even pick them out.
For all you know,
I could be a fashion...
... monger.
I would love for you to go with me.
What?
What should I wear?
Now I'm all nervous.
You know, they say
"A watched pot never beeps."
It's been a couple hours...
...and she hasn't called.
Not that I even care. I don't.
Why don't you just call her?
You obviously want to.
You think you know me so well.
Well, don't you wanna?
So I do know you.
That's what I said.
Well, so?
I can't.
I can't. She dumped me.
I totally trusted her,
then one day it was like:
"Okay, bye, Pheebs."
Gone!
You know what the saddest part is?
When we were playing together,
that was...
...the most fun I've ever had
in all my lives.
My favorite shoes, so good to me
I wear them every day
Down at the heel, holes in the toes
Don't care what people say
My feet's best friend
Pals to the end
With them, I'm one hot chickie
Though late one night
Not much light
I stepped in something icky
Sticky shoes, sticky shoes
Always make me smile
Next time I'll...
...avoid the...
...pile!
We're beginning to see a lot of
layering of sheer fabrics and colors.
For instance, a sheer navy blouse
over a pink....
I'm really glad we came.
You're so pretty.
I love you.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
It's not your fault
That's great!
You know, you could totally sell this.
It'd be perfect for, like,
a kitty-litter campaign.
A jingle?
Why not?
You'd make a ton of money.
If I was in this for the money,
I'd be a millionaire by now.
You gotta get out of
that jingle-head.
You're right.
You're right. I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I'm gonna play a song now
that's really, really sad.
It's called "Magician Box Mix-Up."
Oversized bracelets,
oversized earrings...
...oversizing of accessories,
in general, is very popular now.
Can I borrow this?
My milk's gone bad.
I hate that.
I once had a thing of half-and-half.
Stole my car.
So how was your date with Ginger?
Great.
It was great. She's....
She's great. Great looks
and personality. Greatness.
Sounds like she's got the...
...whole package.
Joey told you about the leg, huh?
Oh, God!
It freaked me out.
It shouldn't, but it did.
I wanna keep seeing her,
but it's like:
"Hey, you know what?
Where's your leg?"
I'm the smallest person in the world,
aren't l?
Morning.
Actually, he's the smallest person
in the world.
Heard about the leg-burning, huh?
It came up.
Listen, I know it's a long shot, but...
... by any chance,
did she find that funny?
So I nodded off a little!
"Nodded off"?
Ross, you were snoring!
My father's boat didn't make
that much noise when it hit rocks!
Come on! Forty-five minutes....
Forty-five minutes, the man talked
about strappy-backed dresses.
Okay, how about four hours
in a freezing museum auditorium...
...Iistening to
Professor "Pitstains" say:
"Remember that thing that died
a gazillion years ago?
Well, here's a little bone
we didn't know it had!"
First of all, it's Professor Pitain.
And second of all,
that little bone proved that...
...that particular dinosaur had wings
but didn't fly.
Okay, you know what I just heard?
A hundred million people
went to see a movie about what I do.
I wonder how many people would go see
a movie called Jurassic Parka.
Oh, that is so
A bunch of out-of-control jackets
take over an island!
If what I do is so lame...
...then why did you insist on coming
with me this morning?
Was it so I just wouldn't
go with Mark?
I wanted to be with you.
I don't know, I feel like lately...
...you're slipping away from me...
...with this new job
and all these new people.
And you've got this
whole other life going on.
I know it's dumb...
...but I just hate
that I'm not a part of it.
It's not dumb.
But maybe it's okay
that you're not a part of it.
You know what I mean?
I mean, it's like...
... I like that you're not
involved in that part of my life.
That's a little clearer.
See, it doesn't mean
I don't love you...
... because I do.
I love you so much.
But my work
It's for me, you know?
I'm out there on my own,
and I'm doing it.
And it's scary,
but I love it because it's mine.
But I mean, is that okay?
Sure.
You're thinking about my leg.
Actually, I forgot.
What's the deal with that again?
Look, it's okay if it bothers you.
I only need to know
how much it bothers you...
...because I don't like
wasting my time.
Am I wasting my time?
No, I don't think so.
It's like anything else.
You just have to get used to it.
What's that?
That's my "nubbin."
What's a nubbin?
It's kind of a third-nipple
kind of thing.
You have three nipples?
Well, you know, two regulars...
...and one that
barely qualifies as a
What?
Nothing. You know, l....
I just remembered.
I have to leave.
You have to leave? Now? How come?
Well, it's nubbin.
Nothing!
You know what?
I'll see you later.
I thought you weren't coming.
-Where were you?
-Come here, come here.
Don't get mad, okay?
Don't give me a reason to get mad,
okay?
I played Smelly Cat for
my old ad agency. They went nuts!
I told you I didn't want you
to try and sell it...
...and you just big, fat did it anyway!
I think, five years ago,
I probably would have done anything...
...to play with you.
But I can do it myself.
If I can't trust you, then forget it.
I don't wanna forget it.
You know what?
You have to choose.
If the most important thing
on the planet to you...
...is this cat-poopy thing,
then you can have Smelly Cat.
But we won't be partners.
So what's it gonna be?
-Smelly cat, smelly cat
-Problem odor in the litter box?
Don't change your kitty,
change your kitty litter.
It's not your fault
Sorry, Pheebs.
You okay?
I actually am.
Because, you know, life's gonna
hand you all kinds of stuff.
You learn your little lessons
and hopefully you grow.
-You wanna hear a new song?
-We'd love to.
Jingle bitch screwed me over
Go to hell, jingle whore
Go to hell, go to hell, go to hell
That's all I have so far.
Well, hello!
-Where you been?
-The doctor.
Is everything okay?
Just had me
a little nubbin-ectomy.
Two nipples, no waiting.
Well! Just like Rachel
in high school.
What?
Come on, I was kidding!
It was such an obvious joke.
That was an obvious joke.
And I didn't think of it. Why?
The source of all my powers.
Oh, dear God, what have I done?